Life got me today
in [snorts] a good way. I was coming out
of Lowe's right here and somebody came
up to me and said, "Hey, I recognize
you, man. I watch all your videos and I
want to thank you for what you're doing
out there." And I you know, this happens
a fair amount and I was like, "Hey, man,
thank you. You know, I'm just a guy."
You know, and we started talking and
we talked about the Bible some and then,
you know, he didn't ask for a picture.
He didn't ask for my number. Dude looked
at me and said, "Hey, man, can I pray
for you?"
And man, right there in the Lowe's
parking lot, dude named Bart.
We took our hats off.
>> [snorts]
>> He held my hand and he sat there and he
prayed for me, dude. So, with all this
going on in my life,
my dad,
my mama, my family, my kids,
everything, all the pain.
I mean, it was just anomalous.
To have just somebody off of
social media meet you in a Lowe's
parking lot and hold your hand and pray
for you.
>> [snorts]
>> And boy, I needed it.
And I just wanted to tell you real
people still exist.
And we're going through real things. You
might see us on the screens, but we're
humans just like you.
And man, life got me today
in [snorts] a good way.
I I think these are tears of healing and
dirt coming out of my eyes.
>> [snorts]
>> But I wanted to say thank you to Bart
and thank you to everyone out there
who's going through something and is
still pushing. And for everybody who
supports me and loves me from a
distance,
can't wait to meet you in a Lowe's
parking lot and pray with you one day.
>> [snorts]